Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Loose prints, 1890 -- 1959; MS036.011; 0.75 Linear Feet; 403 Digital Object(s)
  - Members of the Gamma chapter of the Alpha Kappa Kappa fraternity, 1922; MS036.011.DO.01484; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    Student activities; Greek letter societies; Students; photographic print; Alpha Kappa Kappa; School of Medicine
  - Members of the Delta Epsilon medical fraternity, 1922; MS036.011.DO.01485; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    Student activities; Greek letter societies; People; Students; photographic print; Delta Epsilon; School of Medicine
  - Members of the Zeta Phi medical sorority, 1921 -- 1922; MS036.011.DO.01486; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    Student activities; People; Students; Greek letter societies; photographic print; Zeta Phi; School of Medicine
  - Professor M.S. Munro, 1938; MS036.011.DO.01489; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Professor M.S. Munro on field trip with students, 1937-05-03; MS036.011.DO.01490; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
    Faculty; People; Students; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Professor Melville S. Munro, 1945-06-01; MS036.011.DO.01496; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 60)
  - Professor Mellville S. Munro and his camera, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01497; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
  - Professor Melville S. Munro holding his photography equipment, 1925; MS036.011.DO.01498; Unknown (Box Shared 60)
  - Dr. Timothy Leary at his desk, 1927-12-22; MS036.011.DO.01499; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 60)
    Faculty; photographic print; Leary, Dr. Timothy
  - Football player Fred Ellis, 1926-09-27; MS036.011.DO.01528; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 62)
    Athletics; Football; photographic print; Ellis, Frederick M. "Fish"
  - Freshman delagation, Class of 1924, Kappa of Zeta Psi, 1920 -- 1921; MS036.011.DO.01633; Notman (Box Shared 55)
    9.5x14
    Student activities; photographic print; Zeta Psi
  - Richardson House, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01681; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 113)
  - William Rollin Shipman Memorial inside Goddard Chapel, June, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01711; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 114)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1930; MS036.011.DO.01712; Unknown (Box Shared 114)
  - Prof. Melville S. Munro, Ella H. Munro, Mrs. Ruth Munro, Lawrence M. Munro, 1936; MS036.011.DO.01726; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    photographic print; Munro, Melville S.; Munro, Ella H.; Munro, Ruth M.; Munro, Lawrence M.
  - First Faculty Meeting, 1936-09-17; MS036.011.DO.01787; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 112)
  - Deans of Crane Theological School: Lee S. McCollester and Clarence R. Skinner, 1935-10-30; MS036.011.DO.01789; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
    photographic print; McCollester, Lee Sullivan; Skinner, Clarence R.
  - Deans Lee S. McCollester and Clarence R. Skinner, 1935-10-30; MS036.011.DO.01790; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - New Chemistry Department: Crosby F. Baker, Harris M. Chadwell, David E. Worrell, 1939-12-07; MS036.011.DO.01791; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
  - Department of Chemistry Teachers; Back Row: Chester Littlefield, Earl A. Gulbransen, Harris M. Chadwell, Paul H. Doleman; Front Row: David E. Worrall, Crosby F. Baker, 1939-04-28; MS036.011.DO.01792; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Littlefield, Chester; Gulbransen, Earl A.; Chadwell, Harris M.; Doleman, Paul H.; Worrall, David E.; Baker, Crosby F.; Dept. of Chemistry
  - Deans, 1939; MS036.011.DO.01793; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; photographic print
  - Deans, 1939; MS036.011.DO.01794; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print
  - College Tea, Old Fashioned Costumes, 1938-02-24; MS036.011.DO.01795; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
    College Tea with old fashioned costumes.
    People; photographic print; Neal, Mrs. Herbert V.; Chase, Mrs.; Shaw, Mrs. Edwin A.; Durkee, Henrietta Noble Brown
  - Engineering Faculty, November 23, 1929; MS036.011.DO.01796; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert; College of Engineering
  - First Faculty Meeting, 1936-09-17; MS036.011.DO.01797; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Engineering School Faculty, 1932-04-16; MS036.011.DO.01798; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Faculty, 1935-04-30; MS036.011.DO.01799; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
  - Group of Deans, 1930-11-19; MS036.011.DO.01807; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print; Neal, Herbert C.; Bacon, George Preston; Skinner, Clarence R.; Bush, Edith L.; McCollester, Lee Sullivan; Robinson, Dean; Wren, Frank G.
  - A.B. Faculty, 1929-02-01; MS036.011.DO.01810; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 112)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert; Coll. of Liberal Arts & Jackson College
  - A.B. Faculty, 1927-03-15; MS036.011.DO.01817; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 112)
    Postcard; Writing on the back
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Coll. of Liberal Arts & Jackson College
  - Publishing Office Force, 1920; MS036.011.DO.01819; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    Joan Franceschini on right
    People; photographic print; Franceschini, Joan; Publishing Office
  - Alumni Secretary's Office force, 1930-12-09; MS036.011.DO.01820; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    Betty Davis on left with typewriter
    People; photographic print; Davis, Betty; Office of Alumni Relations
  - Constance Kenney [Publishing Office], 1935; MS036.011.DO.01821; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; photographic print; Kenney, Constance; Publishing Office
  - Murdena Campbell, Chem. Lab Office, 1939-04-28; MS036.011.DO.01825; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; photographic print; Campbell, Murdena; Dept. of Chemistry
  - Murdena Campbell, 1939-04-28; MS036.011.DO.01826; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Emily Bettencourt, Alumni Office Force, 1937-03-22; MS036.011.DO.01827; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; photographic print; Bettencourt, Emily; Office of Alumni Relations
  - Adelaide Greene Timsun, 1929; MS036.011.DO.01828; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 115)
    Press Release Included
    People; photographic print; Timsun, Adelaide Greene
  - Ruth E. Sherry at desk, 1937-10-21; MS036.011.DO.01830; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    photographic print; Ruth, Sherry E.
  - Constance Kenney, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01831; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
    photographic print; Kenney, Constance
  - Gertrude Elliott and Marion Osbeck; Publishing Office, 1940; MS036.011.DO.01832; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Jean Franceschini; Publishing Office, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01833; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
  - Retiring Staff, 1935; MS036.011.DO.01835; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
    photographic print; Mergendahl, Mrs. Litus E.; MacNaughton, Professor Edgar; Reynolds, Nellie; Mergendhal; Graustein, Dr. mary C.; Weaver, Prof. Frederick N.; Yeager, Stanton W.; Stearns, Albert Warren; Stearns, Mrs.; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Richmond, Mrs. Paul; Files, Professor Myron J.; King, Mrs. Rufus; King, Captain Rufus; Averill, Harvey E.; Miller, George Stewart; Files, Mrs. Myron J.; Richmond, Dr.; Averill, Mrs. Harvey; Farnham, Professor Walter E.
  - Morris at the Gate, 1937-06-12; MS036.011.DO.01836; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
  - Digging Representative River, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01871; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Rapid Bridge Construction, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01872; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Rapid Bridge Construction, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01873; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - World War I, bleachers, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01874; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - War Gardens, Dr. Lambert [director], 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01875; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Lambert, Fred D.
  - Physical Education, Capt. Bowman, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01876; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Bowman, Captain
  - Making a canopy over front of Power House, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01877; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Power House Extension, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01878; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Power House Extension, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01879; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Auto-mechanic training, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01880; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Auto-mechanics training, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01881; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Auto-mechanics training, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01882; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Bromfield Pearson and Power House Grounds: Auto Laboratory, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01883; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - World War I, Mechanics, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01884; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Digging Foundation of New Building, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01885; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Digging Foundation of new building, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01886; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Setting Electric light poles, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01887; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Removing old tree, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01888; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - New building construction, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01889; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - New building nearly done, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01890; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
  - Saturday Afternoon Sports, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01891; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Saturday afternoon sports, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01892; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Fans in the Stands, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01893; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
  - Laundry Work Specials, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01894; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
  - Laundry, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01895; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - World War I, milling soldiers, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01896; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - World War I, College Ave and Boston Ave, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01897; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Fist 100 men, New Hampshire division getting ready, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01898; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - End of the registration line, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01899; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Falling in for drill- new men, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01900; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30)
  - World War I, Soldiers outside of West Hall, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01901; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
  - World War I, First Drill, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01902; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
  - Recieving Instruction, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01903; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Major Bowman Adresses Men, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01904; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
  - Lieutenant H. E. Park, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01907; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Park, Lieutenant H. E.
  - Ensign McCutcheon, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01908; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; McCutcheon, Ensign
  - Battalion Parade and Inspection, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01909; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Captain Chamberlain, 1914 -- 1918; MS036.011.DO.01910; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
  - Jackson forming for Armistice Parade, 1918; MS036.011.DO.01911; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 116)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Pre-registration; President Charmicheal with Class in Chapel, 1939-09-21; MS036.011.DO.01916; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard
  - Basketball Players, April, 1927; MS036.011.DO.01919; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 28)
    Writing on the back with illegible names
  - Ground breaking, Cousens Gymnasium with President Cousens at the controls, 1931; MS036.011.DO.01961; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30)
  - Ballou Hall, 1931; MS036.011.DO.01974; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30)
    photographic print; Munro, Melville S.
  - Dedication of Bowen Porch, 1939-10-28; MS036.011.DO.01978; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    Buildings; People; College presidents; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard; Bowen, Eugene B.
  - Dedication of Bowen Porch, 1939-10-28; MS036.011.DO.01979; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall, North side Bowen Porch, 1937; MS036.011.DO.01980; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Dedication of Bowen Porch, 1939-10-28; MS036.011.DO.01981; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall, Bowen Porch, 1940-06-15; MS036.011.DO.01985; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Eaton Library in the snow, Febuary, 1930; MS036.011.DO.02013; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30)
    Buildings; Libraries; photographic print
  - Eaton Library Window with Ivy, 1935-06-01; MS036.011.DO.02015; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30)
  - The League of Nations: Child's Clinic Representation of various nationalities., 1930; MS036.011.DO.02031; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 30)
  - Cast of 1932 Pageant, MS036.011.DO.02033; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
    photographic print; Simonds, R.; Gaylor, E. L.; Wood, H.; Ginsburg, R.; Haber, M.; Spector, Dr. B.; Benin, H.; Stern, A.; Connelly, T.G.; Campbell, F. L.; Bovaird, J. E.; Faraci, P.; Chase, W.P; Tompkins, M.I.; Goodman, D.R.; Chapman, C.E.; Bolger, M.E.; Eastwood, M.V.
  - Circulation desk in Eaton Library, 1934-12-04; MS036.011.DO.02513; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 32)
    (staff members identified only as Atherton, Maclead, and Walkley/student identified as Sinclair)
    Libraries; People; photographic print; Library
  - Alfred C. Lane and Harry P. Burden, 1937-09-14; MS036.011.DO.02721; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Lane, Alfred Church; Lane, Alfred Church; Dept. of Geology; Dept. of Electrical Engineering
  - Alfred C. Lane, 1938-10-06; MS036.011.DO.02722; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating the Stearns Estate, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02723; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane with four unidentified men in front of a car, 1931 -- 1932; MS036.011.DO.02725; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating a site near Governor's Avenue in Medford, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02726; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating a site near Governor's Avenue in Medford, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02727; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating the Stearns Estate, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02728; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating a site near Governor's Avenue in Medford, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02729; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating a site near Governor's Avenue, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02730; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating a site near Governor's Avenue, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02731; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. "Pop" Lane, 1934; MS036.011.DO.02732; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane excavating the Stearns Estate, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02733; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Alfred C. Lane at the Stearns Estate, 1934-11-22; MS036.011.DO.02734; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor and music historian Harry A. Hersey, 1920; MS036.011.DO.02751; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Hersey, Harry Adams; Department of Music
  - Harry Hersey and Helen Hersey, 1940-06-17; MS036.011.DO.02754; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
    People; Faculty; Students; Commencement; photographic print; Hersey, Harry Adams; Hersey, Helen; Department of Music
  - Professors Row, 1890; MS036.011.DO.02871; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
    Views; Roads; Houses; photographic print
  - Goddard Chapel, 1910; MS036.011.DO.02872; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
    Buildings; Churches; photographic print
  - President John Cousens, 1935; MS036.011.DO.02875; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 29)
    People; College presidents; Faculty; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert; Office of the President
  - Miner and Paige Halls and Crane Chapel, 1931; MS036.011.DO.02879; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 64)
    Buildings; Chapels; photographic print; Divinity School
  - The Emperor Jones, playbill. December 13-14, 1928; MS036.011.DO.02948; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 38)
    Student activities; photographic print; Tufts College
  - Teachers helping young students string beads at the Ruggles Street School, 1926; MS036.011.DO.03007; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 33, Box Shared 117)
    Date is approximate; 3x5 photo and 3x5 copy negative
    People; Students; Children; Child Development; Eliot Pearson Department of Child Development, records; photographic print; copy negative; Ruggles Street School; Eliot-Pearson Children's School; Eliot-Pearson Dept. of Child Development
  - Room of two Jackson students living in Graves House, 1932-05-13; MS036.011.DO.03343; Munro, Melville S.
    Houses; Dormitories; Rooms; Jackson College
  - Members of the Ivy Society who are in charge of Junior Day, 1929-05-17; MS036.011.DO.03348; Munro, Melville S.
    (left to right) top: R. Russell, E. Littleton, H. Arlanson, H. Godfrey, R. Meserve; bottom: R Ockert, W. Morton, T. Reese, G. Welsh, A. Farguhar
    People; Students; Russell, Robert Pratt; Littleton, Earle F.; Arlanson, Harry; Godfrey, Howard; Meserve, Robert W.; Ockert, Raymond G.; Morton, Warren W.; Reese, Thomas J.; Welch, Gilman P.; Farquhar, Andrew J.; Ivy Society
  - Janet Maclachlan and Jacob Gordoy in a dramatic production of "Kind Lady", 1935; MS036.011.DO.03349; Munro, Melville S.
    People; Students; Theater; Maclachlan, Janet; Gordoy, Jacob; Dept. of Drama
  - Tufts track team, 1913; MS036.011.DO.03470; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 33)
    People; Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Track
  - Gager Gate, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03909; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Ice storm on campus, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03910; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Ice storm on campus, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03911; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Eaton Hall and Goddard Chapel, exterior views, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03912; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 65)
  - Dearborn Gate covered in snow, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03913; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Dearborn Gate covered in snow, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03914; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Dearborn Gate, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03915; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Exterior view of Goddard Chapel, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03916; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Bell tower of Goddard Chapel, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03917; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
    Bell towers; Chapels; photographic print
  - Exterior view of Goddard Chapel, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03918; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Exterior view of West Hall, 1935; MS036.011.DO.03919; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 18)
  - Tufts football team, 1927-10-26; MS036.011.DO.03965; Munro, Melville S.
    Students; Football; Athletics; Men; Football
  - First string lineup, football team, 1927-10-26; MS036.011.DO.03966; Munro, Melville S.
  - Kick off, Boston University vs. Tufts football game, 1927-10-29; MS036.011.DO.03967; Munro, Melville S.
  - Tufts football team, University of New Hampshire, 1927-10-05; MS036.011.DO.03968; Munro, Melville S.
  - University of New Hampshire v. Tufts, football game, 1934-11-03; MS036.011.DO.03969; Munro, Melville S.
  - Line up for the opening football game, 1934-10-03; MS036.011.DO.03970; Munro, Melville S.
  - University of New Hampshire v. Tufts, 1934-11-03; MS036.011.DO.03971; Munro, Melville S.
  - Tufts undefeated 1927 football team, MS036.011.DO.04423; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 69)
    Athletics; People; Men; Football; Students; photographic print
  - Tufts undefeated track team, 1935 -- 1936; MS036.011.DO.04606; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 70)
  - Football team in front of Barnum Hall, 1925; MS036.011.DO.04612; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 37)
  - Tufts men's indoor track team, 1934 -- 1935; MS036.011.DO.04618; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 37)
  - Coach Arthur Sampson and team, 1929; MS036.011.DO.04626; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 37)
    People; Students; Athletics; Football; photographic print; Sampson, Arthur G.
  - West Hall, 1931; MS036.011.DO.04665; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 124)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Gates; photographic print; Tufts University
  - East Hall repairs, 1937; MS036.011.DO.04668; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
    3.5x5
    Buildings; Dormitories; Workers; Scaffolds; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Ballou Hall, 1940; MS036.011.DO.04678; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Administrative; Academic; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Ballou Hall, 1940; MS036.011.DO.04680; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
  - Southeast view of Ballou Hall, 1930; MS036.011.DO.04681; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Ballou Hall decorated for unknown occasion, 1935; MS036.011.DO.04683; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
    Date is approximate; 10x8
    Buildings; Administrative; Academic; Decorations; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Ballou Hall, 1930; MS036.011.DO.04684; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
  - Ballou Hall, 1939; MS036.011.DO.04685; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
  - Replica of old electrical lab in Ballou Hall for Engineering Night, 1936-04-26; MS036.011.DO.04686; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Academic; Laboratories; Interior views; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Three students trying golf clubs in the bookstore, 1934; MS036.011.DO.04688; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 125)
    Students identified as Campman, Elliott, Bowers.
    Students; Bookstore; photographic print; Tufts University; Bookstore
  - Jackson College students on Baby Day, 1924; MS036.011.DO.05058; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 71)
    Baby Party; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Jackson varsity basketball squad, Mabel Darby, Bertha Townsend, Evelyn Hagen, Blanche Downing, Barbara Burns, Bertha Patts, 1938-03-03; MS036.011.DO.05059; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 71)
    People; Students; Women; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Darby, Mabel; Townsend, Bertha; Hagen, Evelyn; Downing, Blanche; Burns, Barbara; Patts, Bertha; Jackson College
  - Southwest view of campus, front of Ballou Hall, near Dearborn Gate, 1938-09-22; MS036.011.DO.05063; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    Buildings; Exterior views; photographic print
  - Miner Hall, 1930; MS036.011.DO.05070; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
  - Goddard Chapel after hurricane of 1938, 1938-09-22; MS036.011.DO.05071; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    Chapels; Exterior views; Hurricanes; photographic print
  - Corner of Dearborn and Bromfield Roads, after hurricane of 1938, "Lineman's Headache", 1938-09-22; MS036.011.DO.05072; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    People; Roads; Hurricanes; photographic print
  - Alumni Gate from Music House after hurricane of 1938, 1938-09-22; MS036.011.DO.05073; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    Buildings; Exterior views; Gates; Hurricanes; photographic print
  - Braker Hall, 1930; MS036.011.DO.05121; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    Picture postcards; Buildings; Exterior views; photographic print
  - Football season opening. (r to l) Coach Lewis F. Manly sitting on ball, Coach Arthur G. Sampson addressing the boys, and team candidates, 1927; MS036.011.DO.05122; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    Picture postcards; Football; Athletics; People; Students; photographic print; Manly, Lewis F.; Sampson, Arthur G.